# Fabio T. Hiroki

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

fabiothiroki@gmail.com fabiothiroki.github.io +55 19 98110-0218

### Summary

Hi, I'm a software developer that enjoys working in a autonomous, purpose driven team, crafting meaningful applications. As a programmer, I've worked with front-end, back-end and specialized in native mobile development. I've also acted as a team leader. My personal goal as a professional is to continuously improve myself and develop the potential of those around me.

### Knowledge

I can develop apps using Java/Kotlin in Android, and Swift/Objective-C in iOS. As they are object-oriented languages, I am careful to create clean and mainatable code, mainly by applying SOLID Principles, Design Patterns and Unit Tests. I also have a good experience with Continuous Integration (TravisCi and Jenkins), Backend (NodeJS, SQL, MongoDB). If needed, I know my way around Angular, Docker, and Kubernetes.

## Work Experience

### Nic.br Project Analyst

Jun 2016 - Present

Have worked so far in software consultancy companies, I was searching for a product focused organization in which I could have more ownership and improve over the life cycle of a single product. The greatest technical challenge here was to maintain and improve a legacy system with a high request rate and a small team, using concepts like: real-time monitoring, log management, quality metrics, automation and microservices.

# Taqtile Mobility Project Leader and Developer

Jan 2013 - Jun 2016

At Taqtile I have started with an Android/iOS development internship. As I became more proficient with the proficient with the technologies, I have started leading projects, taking responsibility for technical and architectural decisions, balancing the app quality and deadlines and managing the project using agile practices. This leadership experience made me passionate about team work and people management.

### Early Career

### Innovatech Telecom / C2C Balloon Full Stack Web Development Internship

Feb 2010 - Mar 2012

These internships allowed me to create a foundation for my knowledge about web development and user experience (UX) in the startup environment.

#### Education

# University of Campinas (UNICAMP)

Bachelor, Computer Engineering

 $\ensuremath{\mathsf{UNICAMP}}$  is ranked among the top 200 universities in the world by the QS World University Rankings.